freedreamjobs.com 2013-12-25

# FreeDreamJobs.com - Privacy Policy

FreeDreamJobs.com is committed to your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect from and about you when you visit our website www.FreeDreamJobs.com.com (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy also explains how FreeDreamJobs.com may use and disclose such information, as well as your ability to control certain uses of it.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION

**Personal Information**  
FreeDreamJobs.com, or a third party service provider acting on our behalf ("Service Provider"), collects personal information from you when you choose to share it with us to use our matching services, create an online account with us, order products or services from us, request information from us, sign up for newsletters or our email list, participate in a survey, or otherwise contact us. The personal information we collect may include your name, address, telephone number, email address, date of birth, education level and year of graduation, information you include on your resume, and, if you are a FreeDreamJobs.com customer, credit/debit card number. We may combine your personal information with additional personal information and non-personal information we collect or receive about you from other online and offline sources.

**Information Automatically Collected**  
We, or our Service Providers, may use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, local shared objects (Flash cookies), or other technologies to collect certain information about visitors to our Site, use of our online services, and interactions with our emails and online advertisements. For example, we or our Service Providers may automatically collect certain non-personal information from you, including but not limited to your browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol ("IP") address and the domain name from which you accessed the Site. In addition, we or our Service Providers may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit the Site, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Site, the number of times you return to the Site, other click-stream or site usage data, emails that you open, forward or click-through to our Site.

We may also use third party advertisements to support our Site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, or local shared objects when they advertise on our Site, which may send these advertisers information including your non-personal information.

You are free to set your Internet browser to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Site or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. To learn more about the use of cookies or other technologies to deliver more relevant advertising and to know your choices about not having this information used by certain Service Providers, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and [here](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html). To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, please click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html).

**Information Collected From Other Sources**  
We may obtain information about you from other sources, including commercially available sources such as data aggregators and public databases. This information may include name, demographic information, updated contact information, interests, and publicly-observed data, such as from social media and online activity. We may combine this information with the information we collect from and about you to help us tailor our communications to you and to improve our services and products.

### INFORMATION USE 

FreeDreamJobs.com or its Service Providers may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes:

  * To fulfill orders, provide service and communicate with customers;
  * To develop new products or services;
  * To respond to your inquiries;
  * To provide you with customized Site content, targeted offers, and advertising on the Site or on other sites;
  * To contact you with information, newsletters and promotional materials from our company or on behalf of our partners and affiliates;
  * To contact you when necessary;
  * To obtain feedback on the quality of the communication you received from employment or educational organizations from whom you have requested information or we have matched based on your interests;
  * To review the usage and operations of our Site and services and improve our Site content, products and services;
  * To address problems with the Site, our business or our products and services;
  * To manage our telecommunications networks;
  * To protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business;
  * As described to you at the point of data collection; and
  * To use and disclose your credit/debit card information only to process payments and prevent fraud.

We may contact you via email, telephone, text message, postal mail, or any other means of communication that you provide to us as a means of contacting you.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication.

### INFORMATION DISCLOSURE

FreeDreamJobs.com may disclose the information we collect from and about you as follows: (1) to the employment or educational organizations from whom you have requested information or the employment or educational organization we have matched based on your interests; (2) to our email and data hosting service providers, if the disclosure will enable them to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us; (3) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of the FreeDreamJobs.com Site Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (4) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; (5) to our select partners and affiliates that we believe may have offers of interest to you; and (6) as described to you at the point of collection.

FreeDreamJobs.com may share aggregate or anonymous non-personal information with third parties.

Also, FreeDreamJobs.com may sell or purchase assets during the normal course of our business. If another entity acquires us or any of our assets, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personal information provided through this Site in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

If you are a California resident, you may opt-out of our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To opt out, please contact us at [CAprivacy@freedreamjobs.com](mailto:CAprivacy@freedreamjobs.com).

### Facebook Connect or other OpenID provider

You can log in to our Site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

### Social Media (Features) and Widgets:

Our Site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our Site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the Privacy Policy of the company providing it.

### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

The Site may have links to third-party websites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the practices of such sites.

### OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

Protecting children's privacy is important to us. We do not direct the Site to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, children under the age of thirteen.

### OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY

We have taken certain physical, administrative, and technical steps to safeguard the information we collect from and about our customers and Site visitors. While we make every effort to help ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee our security measures.

When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card information) on our forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

### IF YOU HAVE QUESTIONS

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us at [privacy@freedreamjobs.com](mailto:privacy@freedreamjobs.com).

### REVISIONS TO THIS POLICY

FreeDreamJobs.com reserves the right to revise this policy at any time. When we do, we will post the change(s) on the Site. If we change the policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you posted here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.
